let questions = [
    {
        num: 1,
        question: "O'zbekistonning poytaxti?",
        answer: "Toshkent",
        options: [
            "Baku",
            "Toshkent",
            "Buxarest",
            "Madrid" 
        ]
     },
     {
        num: 2,
        question: "Yaponiya poytaxti?",
        answer: "Tokio",
        options: [
            "Tokio",
            "Seul",
            "Moskva",
            "Berlin"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 3,
        question: "AQSH poytaxti?",
        answer: "Vashington",
        options: [
            "Toshkent",
            "Seul",
            "Madrid",
            "Vashington"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 4,
        question: "Germaniya poytaxti?",
        answer: "Berlin",
        options: [
            "Seul",
            "Buenos-Ayres",
            "Berlin",
            "Braziliya"
        ]
    },   
    {
        num: 5,
        question: "Avstraliya poytaxti?",
        answer: "Kanberra",
        options: [
            "Tehron",
            "Ottava",
            "Kanberra",
            "London"
        ]
    },  
    {
        num: 6,
        question: "Angliya poytaxti?",
        answer: "Tokio",
        options: [
            "Tokio",
            "Seul",
            "Moskva",
            "Berlin"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        num: 7,
        question: "Ekvador poytaxti?",
        answer: "Kito",
        options: [
            "Vellington",
            "Kito",
            "Gavana",
            "Abu-Dabi"
        ]
    },  
    {
        num: 8,
        question: "Italiya poytaxti?",
        answer: "Rim",
        options: [
            "Kanberra",
            "Rim",
            "Santiago",
            "Berlin"
        ]
    },  
    {
        num: 9,
        question: "Janubiy Koreya poytaxti?",
        answer: "Tokio",
        options: [
            "Berlin",
            "Madrid",
            "Seul",
            "Lissabon"
        ]
    },         
    {
        num: 10,
        question: "Potugaliya poytaxti?",
        answer: "Lissabon",
        options: [
            "Lissabon",
            "Kito",
            "Praga",
            "Tehron"
        ]
    }, 

]